<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blake Braun</title>
    <link>http://blakebraun.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Blake Braun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 20:30:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://blakebraun.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://blakebraun.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 20:30:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blakebraun.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
Please feel free to contact me using the information below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:blake@blakebraun.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;blake@blakebraun.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
LinkedIn: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/bbraun5&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;bbraun5&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Work</title>
      <link>http://blakebraun.com/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 20:30:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blakebraun.com/work/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;blakebraun.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click to download my resume.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Vice President of Administration for the Delta Delta chapter of  Alpha Phi Omega, I completely redesigned the &lt;a href=&#34;http://apo.slu.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;chapter website&lt;/a&gt;, making it more visually appealing and easier to navigate.
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, I also maintain the &lt;a href=&#34;http://facebook.com/apodeltadelta&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Alpha Phi Omega - Delta Delta Facebook page.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
As a &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.slu.edu/beabilliken/be-a-billiken-blog&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;‘Be a Billiken Blogger’&lt;/a&gt; for Saint Louis University’s Division of Marketing &amp;amp; Communications, I provide a current student’s perspective on undergraduate life at the University for prospective students. &lt;a href=&#34;http://babblake.tumblr.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click to view my personal blog for the University.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a newswriting course, I maintain a &lt;a href=&#34;http://blakebraun.wordpress.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; related to topics in the university community as well as general tips on newswriting as a practice.
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, for fun, I created a &lt;a href=&#34;img/filter.jpg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Snapchat filter&lt;/a&gt; that is active on the campus of Saint Louis University.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://blakebraun.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 20:28:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blakebraun.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;blakebraun.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click to download my resume.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Computer Science and Communication double major at &lt;a href=&#34;http://slu.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Saint Louis University&lt;/a&gt;, I have a passion for both technical and creative work. I am interested in creating tools and applications that make peoples&amp;rsquo; lives easier and more enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
I have worked in a variety of positions with duties ranging from waiting tables to migrating Google Apps users to Office 365. Customer service experience has given me the ability to work with others and cooperate in team settings, while my technical experience ensures that I know how to get the job done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Through my courses, I have gained a wide variety of insight into both the information technology and communications fields. I have become proficient in Java, C/C++, Python, and more. I have also been able to practice my photography, videography, and newswriting, while strengthening other communication skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Personal interests and hobbies include music, photography, and more. I am a member of the Saint Louis University pep band, the Vice President of Administration for the Delta Delta chapter of Alpha Phi Omega, and a student blogger for Saint Louis University’s Division of Marketing and Communications, among other things. For more of my work, please see my &lt;a href=&#34;work/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;work page.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>