<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Blake Braun</title>
    <link>http://blakebraun.com/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Blake Braun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 20:28:34 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://blakebraun.com/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://blakebraun.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 20:28:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blakebraun.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;blakebraun.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click to download my resume.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Computer Science and Communication double major at &lt;a href=&#34;http://slu.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Saint Louis University&lt;/a&gt;, I have a passion for both technical and creative work. I am interested in creating tools and applications that make peoples&amp;rsquo; lives easier and more enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
I have worked in a variety of positions with duties ranging from waiting tables to migrating Google Apps users to Office 365. Customer service experience has given me the ability to work with others and cooperate in team settings, while my technical experience ensures that I know how to get the job done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Through my courses, I have gained a wide variety of insight into both the information technology and communications fields. I have become proficient in Java, C/C++, Python, and more. I have also been able to practice my photography, videography, and newswriting, while strengthening other communication skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Personal interests and hobbies include music, photography, and more. I am a member of the Saint Louis University pep band, the Vice President of Administration for the Delta Delta chapter of the Alpha Phi Omega service fraternity, and a student blogger for Saint Louis University’s Division of Marketing and Communications, among other things. For more of my work, please see my &lt;a href=&#34;work/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;work page.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>